(Amy:)So, how do we start?
(Emily:)We have to look for the clues
hidden around the room.
(Raj:)Uh, wasn't there
supposed to be a zombie?
(growling)
(yelling)
Ooh!
(Raj:)Okay, let's hope
one of the clues
(Raj:)is written on a pair
of clean underwear.
(Clerk:)Mr. and Mrs. Wolowitz?
(Clerk:)As far as I can tell,
your bag arrived in Los Angeles.
(Bernadette:)So, where is it?
(Clerk:)I don't know, perhaps somebody
(Clerk:)took it off the carousel
by mistake?
(Howard:)So, some stranger has my mom?
(Howard:)Is that what you're telling me?
(Howard:)My poor mother can be anywhere
in Los Angeles right now?
I-I wish I was telling you that.
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Clerk:)but the passenger
could've gotten
(Clerk:)on an international flight.
Oh, okay, great!
(Howard:)So, your entire job is
to find lost luggage,
(Howard:)and you've narrowed
down the location
(Howard:)of my mother to
the planet Earth!
I'm sorry!
W-Would 500
frequent-flyer miles help?
(Clerk:)That could get you
to Sacramento.